Then what happened at this time,
good afternoon, good afternoon Harshita ji, so
see the recommendation
on ICICI, now
I am talking about ICICI Lombard because see,
if you see the pattern here, a
bottom has been formed around 1120, after that
in the consultation of 5-6 days, ICICI was giving resistance on 20 team average,
but the average has been in the middle,
just a few minutes ago, in this step it
went to 22, I have regressed it and taken it out
above it, volume was seen there,
so you have to buy with a stop loss of 11, 11, 39, the
target in ICICI will be 1170 and here you
can also take option trade, the
December
1160 call option of ICICI is settling around 38 pieces,
buy there for a
target of Rs 60 with a stop loss of Rs 29,
okay, ICICI is
giving a good special move on your screen, right now
404.40 of this period means the previous last is
almost
Ritz's Hitech 434 and
RVNL are doing the highest cliff in 10 sessions. In fact, in our description,
we had mentioned this in the first forum as well. It will
also be given in the directory. It is doing TET.
Good mobile in all the railway stocks.
Meanwhile, its move is getting sharper and
reaching 29883. Now Nifty is up by 500 points.
Amit Seth ji, hello, welcome to the program.
Tell me about your call at this time. Good
afternoon everyone.
[Music]
No stop, which took almost its 20th support. It was
consolidating well since last 2 days and today
we are looking at it. So, there is
a bike advice in TCS. Currently the price is
3348. Targets will be 3450 and stop
loss will be of 3300.
Current levels are from 348. You
can go up to 3450. Counter buy side
trade comes behind it. Today one and a half percent
you can trade on that stock.
Tell me your trade.
So the trade will be from PSU banks and in that the
advice to buy Bank of Baroda futures is
good. December seems to be continuing the trend
and the PSU bank basket has shown
us a good buying entry here, so
in the PSU basket,
we are getting attracted to Bank of Baroda.
Here we will buy December futures and
check the target that we are expecting in this, up to 178-180, the stop loss will be
around 166, so along with buying Bank of Baroda
December futures, okay,
Bank of Baroda, well I have received a lot of calls,
Manas also called yesterday on this, now let's
take Nifty it once, I am actually
Pakistan, I am most happy today that what
they must have heard in the morning free market,
they must have made a lot of money today on ITM, there was
a very clear view that there will be a
huge rally in it today and at this time this
index is up by about one and a half percent, now
look at its technical aspect,
in this, its moving average right now is the one on which
it got stuck last time.
If you follow the simple moving average at ₹30000,
it shows a little more traction. In the
moving averages of the near term, a
little explanation is given. Moving everything is done.
Focus on simple moving in the long term.
Here, the 200 moving average is
its place, simple moving average
30000 370 and its August high was
around 30000 256 and now we
are at 29894, that is, almost now we are bringing it
back to the project. If this
project is
coming out of Nifty this time, then a gain of three-four
percent will automatically occur.